This is the third victim,
whom was gruesomely murdered
in the middle of the city.
The murderer used ruthless
and bizarre murder methods.
Forensic officers are currently working hard.
But still, no evidence has been collected
since the first corpse,
except the knitted yarn that the murderer left behind
to mock the authorities.
The media therefore called this serial killer
the Yarns Murderer.
We the common people can only pray
and hope that the police can arrest the culprit soon.
reported by Saowani Eadlao.
Thank you, Ms. Saowani.
This is the most shocking murder
in more than twenty years
since we have had the Killer Genes Act.
So today, let's go back
and get to know this law again.
Going back almost thirty years ago,
Thailand faced an economic crisis in 1997
and also had a very high crime rate.
And it's getting more serious day by day.
As the government spokesperson,
I'm declaring the law to control
those with killer genes.
All Thai citizens must undergo a killer gene test
to enter the next process of population registration.
The government at that time collaborated
with the Crime Science Department.
Enacted laws to test for killer genes in all Thai citizens
to control their behaviors.
A large number of people came out
to strongly oppose and attack the government
because it is considered a violation of freedom.
The public opinion was divided into two sides.
The argument almost led to a riot in the city.
But then finally the law was revised
until it had fewer regulations.
Until it was announced and enforced in 2000,
under the leadership of Dr. Chonlathorn Traikanon
Genetics Specialist,
the Director-General of the Crime
Science Department at that time.
To all Thai people, please rest assured
that the law protects people with this killer gene.
No one's freedom will be violated.
All Thai people
still have equal rights and freedoms as before.
And I promise you
that in five years from now,
if the crime growth rate does not decrease significantly
This is me.
I will be the one to propose the repeal of this law.
The law governing the behavior of those with killer genes has been in place for over twenty years.
The violent crime rate has decreased significantly.
And the crimes that occurred were ordinary, non-violent cases.
We have lived peacefully for a long time.
Until three consecutive murders occurred.
After the announcement of his candidacy for Prime Minister
Dr. Chonlathorn's recently
That could mean that Dr. Chonlathorn's killer gene theory is about to be disproved.
This news is starting to affect
your popularity more and more.
If the murderer is still not caught
I think the results of this election
may not be as you expected.
Take it easy.
Leave it to the police.
But looking at the murder's methods,
the suspect definitely has killer genes.
Wait for the police to catch them.
After the genes are detected from the suspect,
I assure you that the backlash will definitely happen.
And how can you trust that this is not a set-up to discredit you?
Find a scapegoat.
When no genes are detected,
you will be ruined.
And now our spy reports that a special unit will be set up to handle this case specifically.
I think you should send our people to look into the transparency of this case.
From the shocking murder cases of the past month.
Evidence from the forensic science division
and forensic evidence,
it is agreed that all three cases are connected.
And it's highly possible that it's the same murderer.
The Royal Thai Police therefore
declares this case a special case.
It is classified as a serial murder case
and a special investigation unit was set up to take responsibility,
under the care of
Police Lieutenant Colonel Pilanthorn Traikanon
May I have your permission?
"Traikanon"
What is your relationship with Dr. Chonlathorn?
I am his son.
This case is related to your father's popularity base.
Are you sure that you can close the case transparently without scapegoating?
That's right.
Absolutely guaranteed.
With police honor,
My work...
must be guiltless and just.
I promise you.
That no politician will be able to interfere
with my investigation process.
But the politician you're talking about is your father.
So how are you going to answer the people?
Mr. Saran, can you tell me why Dr. Chonlathorn's son has to take charge of this case?
That's right. How can you expect the public to trust you?
That's right. How can this not be a political intervention?
Can you catch the culprit?
People throughout the building are talking about it.
That your father loves popularity more than his own son.
That's why they dare to let you do this extremely difficult case.
But that's it.
Even if we catch the culprit,
and that damn genes cannot be detected.
He could make it happen.
No one can change the test results, sir.
Except the police ourselves.
And on the other hand
Doesn't Dr. Chonlathorn have the right to be suspicious
that there is someone behind it
who do not wish him well and try to make up stories to refute that theory.
The position of Prime Minister is a game that many people are trying to do everything to achieve, sir.
Both father and son are equally arrogant.
Then you should hurry up and drag
the culprit back as soon as possible.
Here.
Your team list.
And if you want to ask for anything more, you can submit a report.
But I have one request.
Close this case as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
The deceased was Mr. Anon Insam, aged 23 years.
The autopsy began at 3:54 p.m.
What kind of forensic photographer are you?
Just seeing this makes you feel shocked.
An.
Since I started working
I've never seen a corpse so brutal before.
What were you thinking when you jumped into this job?
Hey, I studied this field.
I also want to see something new.
It's not a day that I have to sit here and perform
simple autopsies over and over again.
It's not challenging at all.
This is what I've been dreaming about.
You are dreaming of
the bodies or
working with someone particularly?
Mark.
Shut up.
Do your job.
An, look at this.
What is this wound?
It seems like he was bitten.
Ants.
The forensic unit said they found a large ant nest when the body was found.
Shit.
Mark
Help me turn the body over.
Take a photo here
Have the blood test results of the deceased, Mr. Anont Insam, come out yet?
Yes, please hurry.
Lan
We never thought that An would become a forensic scientist for our team.
What a coincidence, we suddenly ended up working together.
Hello, I'm Anya. I'm a forensic doctor.
This is Mark, a forensic photographer.
This is Sergeant Nawin, the chief of forensics in our team.
Here, Sergeant Moo is my assistant.
-Hello.
-Please have a seat.
What are the autopsy results?
This is a photo from the autopsy.
The victim's wrists and ankles were bound with duct tape.
We can see it from the marks on the skin.
So, in conclusion, how did the victim die?
Ants.
What do ants have to do with this?
Er...
When we found the body, we found a lot of ants eating the body, Sergeant.
But we assume that the ants
probably came after the victim died.
No, it's not.
At that time, the victim was still alive.
What does that mean?
The murderer injected Bupivacaine into the victim.
It is a type of local anesthesia used for injection during spinal block to relieve pain.
Now, the person who has received the spinal anesthesia will feel numbness from the lower to the middle of the body.
It depends on the injection spot and the amount used.
In summary,
the victim did not die from being slashed in the abdomen.
But the victim died from being bitten by red ants that bit his internal organs.
What did you say?
We found dirt in our lungs, which was the same dirt we found in the ant nest.
This means that the victim was still
breathing when the red ants bit him.
Slit the abdomen
and use anesthesia to relieve pain
but leaving the victim to death by being bitten by ants, destroying your liver, kidneys, and intestines?
Clearly a psychopath.
To kill the victim in such a bizarre way.
Lan
From this corpse that I autopsied
and the first two corpse reports,
the culprit may be in the medical field.
They seemed to have a great deal of knowledge and expertise about medicine and medical equipment.
So does that mean that if we have a box of pills or a syringe with a number code on it,
We can narrow down the scope of the culprit?
Lieutenant?
We have no evidence of what the doctor said.
All three cases?
Then let's do this, Sergeant.
Go to every hospital near the scene of the incident and ask what medicine is missing.
- Then report to me immediately.
- Noted.
- Lieutenant, the yarn.
- Yes.
Here it is.
We checked for DNA and found nothing.
Then we have to start investigating these yarns.
Inspector?
We've been looking for it for a week now.
But no store has the kind of yarn
that the murderer used.
But...
This shop looks quite big, so maybe there are some.
Sathu, I hope there is.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Hello.
Does your shop have the yarn like this?
Let me see.
Our shop doesn't have this type. We only have regular yarn and Venus yarn.
You've been looking for so long.
-Sergeant.
-I think it looks pretty.
Did your girlfriend knit? Her knitting is beautiful.
She used imported yarn.
It's expensive and hard to find.
- Imported yarn?
- Yes.
In Thailand, do you happen to know
which store we can buy it?
Um
I can't think of any. It's unlikely.
Not likely, okay.
- Anyway, thank you very much.
- Pleasure.
- Oh wait, wait, wait.
- Yes?
There is one shop.
There should be.
This is the shop that the lady mentioned.
Hello.
Hello, are you the owner of the shop?
- Hello.
Is there anything I can help you with?
I am the owner of the shop.
If you want anything,
what kind of yarn do you want, just ask.
Sure.
Do you have this yarn?
I am Police Lieutenant Colonel Pilanthorn Traikanon.
I'm working on a case.
I would like to ask the shop to
kindly cooperate with the police.
Yes.
From the picture, it's not very clear.
I can't tell if it's the same type of yarn
that we have in our shop.
When you knit it into pieces,
it's hard to separate each yarn.
If it's still in lines,
we can tell what kind of yarn it is.
And what if you just look at this picture?
Does the shop have anything similar?
There might be, but they're different colors.
This kind of yarn is hard to find.
You have to order from overseas.
So we just have to take orders.
Not sure if it's all sold out yet.
Could you please check for me
to see if there are any left?
Sure, I'll go check it out for you.
I wonder if there are still some left.
Nowadays, people prefer to order via the Internet.
They are all from abroad.
This kind of yarn
now is rare and must be imported.
And what are these knitted patterns here?
This should be.
Oh, Sky.
Morse code.
It is a method of sending messages through a series of sound signals, lights, or knocks.
It has the characteristics of lines and dots. It is a language that is used all over the world.
It can be compared with the sounds of letters.
This code was first used around 1830 by Samuel F.B. Morse.
This yarn is knitted in Morse code.
Sky.
Sky, dear!
This is my daughter. Her name is Sky.
Sky is interested in decoding
and the letters that exist in this world.
Sky.
Is there Morse code hidden in the yarn?
Sky is an autistic teenager.
- That's why she's strange.
- Sergeant.
Sky probably doesn't want to talk to the police.
I think you guys should go back.
She just keeps decoding for fun.
Finished.
Three pieces of knitted yarn.
Getting started with knitting
knitted with yarn number 8 US, size 5 mm.
knitted this pattern and pearl pattern
alternately until the number is base 2.
The lower part is crocheted.
a crochet hook size 6, size 3 mm.
and a crochet hook size 7, size 4 mm.
This sheet uses size 8-ply blue yarn mixed with gold and copper metallic groupy T-shirt yarn.
This sheet uses 8 ply yarn
mixed with blood-red Tisranaklosa yarn.
This sheet uses a small T-shirt yarn
from the brand Journin Cotton.
All sheets are knitted with short and long spacing.
It's a Morse code signal.
Uh... So what's the code for it?
Where did it go?
What's missing?
There must be four sheets in total.
The third sheet
3/10 is missing.
Don't tell me that
you are thinking about what the kid was saying.
That kid is autistic, Inspector.
I think you shouldn't pay any attention to it.
How many times have I told you?
Do not interact with strangers.
He's not a stranger. He's a customer.
Mother told me to welcome the customers nicely
and they will give me money.
Sky remembers that
mother often said that money is god.
Sky
This is not a child play.
If you keep doing this,
keep meddling in other people's business.
I will take all the lollipops and throw them away.
I'm not meddling anymore.
Mom, don't throw away Sky's lollipop.
Excuse me.
Hello. Sky, stay put. Don't make a fuss.
How can I help you?
- Hello. I'm Ya's father.
- Yes.
I wonder if my daughter has been here at all.
Her friends said that she often comes here.
What is your daughter's name again?
Ya, Isriya.
This person.
Oh
Yes, she comes here regularly,
but I haven't seen her for two weeks now.
She ordered something but hasn't come to collect it.
Sky.
These yarns are binary and Morse code?
I think the Inspector listened to that kid too much.
Oh, that's right.
Possibly.
Some symbols are both dots and dashes.
Right.
This base number is correct.
When we look at it as numbers,
these are real numbers.
over
Yes.
And if this is from the first corpse.
The code on this piece of yarn would be 1/10
1/10
Over 10.
Over ten.
Hey!
- Or will the murderer kill all ten people?
- Ten people?
And what else did that kid say?
Impossible
It must have...
four sheets.
Look here, there should be four sheets in total.
The first sheet is 1/10.
Morse code is decoded as
"Count money every day,
why am I not rich?"
The second sheet is 2/10.
The Morse code can be decoded as:
"Welcome. Answer me, who am I?"
But this is 4/10, not 3/10.
The third sheet is missing. Where did it go?
Four sheets mean there are actually four bodies.
Well, if it's like that kid said.
Then it should be like that.
Well, if there really were four bodies.
The police would have found them.
How can a dead person disappear?
I think it's better not to listen to that weird kid.
How weird, Sergeant?
That kid is autistic.
What?
Really, Lan?
Oh, what a waste of time.
Sergeant
I want you to follow the behavior
of the mother and daughter.
And report to me periodically.
Huh?
Why would you want me to go
after the mother and daughter?
I believe that those two
have something suspicious hidden.
Sky.
I'm heading to the store, dear.
Navigation block, direction.
Navigation block...
Bad signs, Bangkok is bad.
Bangkok is bad.
Hello.
I'll take one Khanom Jeen. Khanom Jeen isn't Chinese.
But it is Mon's.
In the Mon language, it is called Khanom Jeen.
Jeen means ripe.
In the northern dialect, Khanom Jeen is called Khanom Sen.
In the Isan dialect, it is called Khao Pun.
-In the southern dialect, it is called Nom Jeen.
Same as always, Sky.
Take a seat. I'll take it to you.
Here's your spoon.
I have been following this kid for several days now.
Every day she goes to the same place
and does the same thing.
Everything is exactly the same.
Let's just say that if it's not nine in the morning, this kid will never step out of the house.
What about the mother?
How is she?
Quite the opposite.
She stays at the shop all day, then closes the shop in the evening and goes home.
The file will contain the daily reports of both people.
Would you want me to continue?
Continue.
Why do you doubt Sookwan?
Hey, I invited you to eat dessert, not to talk about work.
We don't talk about work.
I've known Lan since high school.
Lan invited me for a meal eight times.
There was never a time when it wasn't about school or work.
So let's talk about Lan's work.
Okay, that's fine.
- I admit that I really doubt Sookwan.
- There it is.
Why don't I win the lottery as easily as guessing you?
Hey, are you into the lottery too?
Let's get to the point.
Okay.
The reason we suspect Sookwan is because
one, the criminal must be an expert in yarn knitting
with different types of yarn.
Two
The suspect must know about
medicine and medical equipment.
So how does this connect you to Sookwan?
It's like this.
I've secretly had staff follow Sookwan, for some time now.
About one week,
there will be 2-3 days when Sookwan visits the same hospital.
She didn't visit there for medication.
Didn't have a doctor's appointment.
And when she comes out, she comes out with a big bag.
It's like something is being carried out.
-That's all?
-No, there's more.
When I first went to see her at the yarn shop.
The first thing I saw was that she was wearing medical gloves.
Working in a yarn shop and most importantly...
This is all we have here.
Oh, please don't touch the yarn if your hands aren't clean.
If the yarn gets dirty, I won't be able to sell it.
Please wash your hands first.
Oh, yes.
-Over there. That's alright.
-Excuse me.
Is that methane?
Is this an operating room disinfectant?
Yes, normally it is mixed with soap
so that it can be used for bleaching.
But normal people don't use it.
That's why I'm suspicious of Sookwan but...
But I'm just curious. I don't believe it yet.
Lan said that her daughter has autism, right?
If we want to investigate the mother,
we have to approach her daughter.
Because kids with autism don't lie.
So how can we approach her daughter or talk to her?
Completed
First, we must make her feel as comfortable as possible without any pressure.
Hello, Sky.
When she looks away, don't stare at her.
Try to talk about things that interest her the most.
Mr. Stranger.
Here it is.
Hello, my name is Pilanthorn.
I am a police officer.
Hello.
My name is Sky. Sky means the space above the Earth.
Sky, do you want this book?
Then I'll buy it and then let's go
find a place to sit and read a book.
I happen to have a lot of questions about decoding that I would like to ask you.
No, my mother doesn't allow me to talk to strangers.
Don't talk to strange people.
Do I look strange?
So you don't want this book anymore?
No, I have to buy something for my mother.
- How much?
- The total payment is 480 baht.
Are all these your mother's?
Thank you.
Dr. Anya.
You wanna see it yourself?
Yes
This is... a different case, right?
Probably is. We didn't find any sheet of yarn.
The deceased was a public relations officer.
Her name is Isriya.
Hello
My name is Sky. Sky means the space above the Earth.
Is Isriya here?
Oh, she's not here.
She hasn't come to work for several days now.
Is there something wrong?
Er...
Mom wanted Isriya to have this yarn.
But if Isriya isn't here, it's okay.
Sky will come again next time.
What's up? Huh?
The fourth corpse?
Yes, if you count the time the body was found.
but if you count the time
the victim died, this is the third body.
The kid was right, Lan.